Sol Gorelick WAG 019
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Human Resources Administration; Income Managment Center; clerical and administrative personnel reports, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Human Resources Administration; Income Maintenance Supervisory Development and Training Program, 1977;1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Human Resources Administration; job openings, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Human Resources Administration; legislative memos, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Human Resources Administration; Manpower and Career Development Agency graduation, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Human Resources Administration; 'Model Cities' program, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Human Resources Administration; monthly control reports, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Human Resources Administration; notice of Intent to Discontinue Public Assistance, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Human Resources Administration; Office of Community Services, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Human Resources Administration; regulations on the use of Christmas decorations memo, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Human Resources Administration; Reorganization Committee, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Human Resources Administration; report on Baltimore D.S.S., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Human Resources Administration; reports on Detroit and Boston D.S.S.'s, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Human Resources Administration; security task force, 1977; 1978 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Human Resources Administration; Shelter allowance policy, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Human Resources Administration; 'Staff Development Reporter' newsletter, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Human Resources Administration; State demonstration employment programs, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Human Resources Administration; summer training program, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Human Resources Administration; supplementary security income data and information, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Human Resources Administration; report on union contracts and government regulations, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Human Resources Administration; informational brochure: 'What is the HRA?', undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Human Resources Administration; Youth Service Agency, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- International Council on Social Welfare, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- ILGWU, Local 66; Leadership training, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Industrial Workers of the World; newsletter, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
- International Federation of Social Workers: 'Missing Chilean Social Workers', 1977 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Interracial home visit with white families/Brooklyn Home Visit Day, December 1964 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Jay Street Employment Eligibility Center, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Jewish Affairs (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Jewish Examiner, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Jewish War Veterans, 1954; 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Job Orientation in Neighborhoods (JOIN), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Joint Economic Committee, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Labor Management Institute: memorandum on municipal collective bargaining, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Labor Research Association, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Leave Cards, 1956-1957; 1963-1967 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Leave Regulations, 1955; 1960; 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Legal Services Staff Association, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Federal legislation, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Legislation; New York City, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Legislation; New York State, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Legislation; unidentified, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Livingstone Special Services Center, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- AFSCME, District 37, Local 371; arbitrations, 1966; 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Local 731; Bulletin, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Local 371; chapters: Greenwood, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Local 371; chapters: supervisors, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Local 371; civil rights, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Local 371; 'Clerical-Administrative Coloring Book for City Employees', undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Local 371; Committtee for effective leadership within Local 371, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Local 371; Committee for Union Democracy, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Local 371; committees; grievances, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Local 371; committees;downtown Brooklyn organizing, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Local 371; committees; fact-finding, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Local 371; committees; finance, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Local 371; committees; legislative, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Local 371; committees; membership, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Local 371; constitutions, 1960; 1961; 1964; 1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Local 371; contracts, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Local 371; correspondence (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Local 371; directory, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Local 371; elections, 1963; 1968; undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Local 371; exam protests, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Local 371; executive board, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Local 371; finances, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Local 371; general, 1940s and 1950s (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Local 371; general, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Local 371; general, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Local 371; Jack Goldberg article: 'A Professional Views the Union', 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Local 371; legislative, undated; 1965 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Local 371; letterhead, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Local 371; lists of names (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Local 371; 'Mechanics of the Job: A guide for Caseworkers', 1965 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Local 371; merger (SSEU), 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Local 371; negotiations, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Local 371; notes, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Local 371; organizational newsletter (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Local 371; reclassification, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Local 371; resolutions, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Local 371; 'The Scene;' publication, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Local 371; 'Welfare Local 371 News;' publication, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Local 371; training, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Local 1193; flyer and newsletter, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Local 1199, hospital division, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Marin Country Department of Public Social Services, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Local 1549; union leaflet, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Marxism; general (Box 8, Folder 48)
- May Day, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Metropolitan Council on Housing, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Michael Schwerner Memorial Fund, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Mid-Brooklyn Times, 1968 (Box 8, Drawer 52)
- Mobilization for Survival, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Model Cities, 1969-1970; undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Movement for Economic Justice, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Multi-Service Center #1, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Municipal Civil Service Commission; Welfare Service Exams, 1952; 1955; 1958; 1968; 1972 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- NASW: 'The Advocate for Human Services' (national newsletter), 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- NASW; Affirmative Action Committee, task force on racism, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- NASW; Board of Directors meetings, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- National Association of Social Workers; Chapter Action Guide, program planning, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- NASW; chapter directory, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- NASW; chapter officers' meetings, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- NASW; conferences and seminars, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- NASW; correspondence between Welfare Policy Committee and Creative Arts Rehabilitation Center, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- NASW; correspondence with city officials and politicians, 1974; 1977; 1980 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- NASW; 'Currents;' NY chapter newsletter, 1974; 1975; 1976; 1978; 1980; 1981 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- NASW; delegate assembly, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- NASW: Delegate assembly, policy statements and resolutions, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- NASW: Delegate assemby (policy, program outlines, etc.), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- NASW: Delegate assembly, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- NASW: Eastern Regional Coalition; minutes, policy proposals, ect., 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- NASW: Eastern Regional Meeting; minutes, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- NASW: "ELAN Alert;" National ELAN newsletter, 1976; 1979; 1980; 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- NASW: Education Legislative Action Network (ELAN); "Lobbying Day" materials, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- NASW: Educational Legislative Action Network (ELAN); meetings, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NASW: Educational Legislative Action Network (ELAN); position bulletins and resolutions, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- NASW; elections, 1975; 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- NASW; executive committee, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- NASW; meetings; open membership, public, international committee, 1974-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- NASWl; health committee, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- NASW; housing committee; welfare, rents, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- NASW; joint meeting with American Orthopsychiatric Association, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- NASW; 'Legislative Day' evaluation forms, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- NASW; membership analysis; response to national office, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- NASW; memorial service for Phyllis Hersh, Chair of Peace and Social Welfare Committee, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- NASW; newsletter, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- NASW; Peace and Social Welfare Committee, undated; 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- NASW; position paper on welfare housing and rents, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- NASW; Helen G. Fooner Memorial Lecture Series, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- NASW; position statements, 1973; 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- NASW; preparatory material for delagate assembly; intra-organizational. professional, and public policy issues, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- NASW; program committee; program priority selection, 1978-1979; 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- NASW; Lewis, Mercer; "Proposal for Restructuring Public Social Services in NYC,", 1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- NASW; restricted payments to AFDC recipients, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- NASW; draft letter to the Research Council, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
- NASW; testimony at the public forum conducted by NYSDSS and NYCHRA (Box 9, Folder 29)
- NASW; testimony; Welfare Refrom Subcommittee of US House of Representatives; H.R. 9030, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- NASW; testimony given by Chapter President Georgia McMurray at HRA public hearing on child abuse, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- National Association of Social Workers; Welfare Grant Increase Coalition, 1977; 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- NASW; Welfare Policy Committee; Campaign for the removal of Blanche Burnstein, Commissoner of NYSDSS, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- NASW; Welfare Policy Committee; City and State Government officials; correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- NASW; Welfare Policy Committee, 1978; 1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- NASW; Welfare Policy Committee; meetings, 1973; 1974-1981 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- NASW; Welfare Policy Committee; position statements and resolutions, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- NASW; Welfare Policy Committee; task force on the urban crisis, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- National Association of Social Workers; Welfare Task Force, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- NASW; year in review bulletin, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- NAACP; NYC Welfare Department Branch, 1963-1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- National Coalition for Economic Justice, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- National Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- National Committee on Fraternities in Education, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- National Conference on Social Welfare (Box 9, Folder 46)
- National Conference on Social Welfare; Cincinnati, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- National Conference on Social Welfare; Daily Bulletin, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- National Conference on Social Welfare; presentation by Chauncey Alexander, executive director of NASW: "The American Liberal: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow", 1979 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- National Economic Growt and Reconstruction Organization (NEGRO), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- National Federation of Social Service Employees, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
- National Paraplegia Foundation: NY Metro Chapter, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- National Public Employees Fringe Benefits Conference, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- National Social Welfare Assembly, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- National Society for the Prevention of Blindness: "Managing the Volunteer Organization" seminar, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Personal information; Sol Gorelick, 1964; 1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- A Plan for Community Social Services, East New York, Human Resources District #3, 3/16/1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Student work study papers, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Treatment centers; memos and map, 1973; 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Memos, 1966; 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Treatment and social services; flyers, news clippings and newsletters (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Treatment and social services; flyers, news clippings and newsletters (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Center Director's Advisory Council (CDAS); Chicago Report, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Bureau of Public Assistance; supervisors' meetings, home visits, education programs; memos and correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- City of New York Department of Welfare, 1951-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Welfare Centers; Training Materials, 4/1964-6/1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Notes for conference with Department of Welfare, 7/21/1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Case Supervisors Training Program, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Assorted correspondence and memos (Box 10, Folder 14)
- New York University Graduate School of Social Work, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- New York Urban Coalition, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- New York Urban League, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Clippings: "How They Wrecked the Welfare Department", 1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Notes, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Notes, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Notes, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Notes, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Notes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Notes, 1977;1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Ocean Hill Alliance for Progress; Welfare League, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Office of Collective Bargaining, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- 163 Bradford Street Association, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- parents for Educational Park, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Peace movements and issues, undated; 1975;1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- People's Town Forum, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- People's Voice...of, for and by the people of East Brooklyn, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Personal (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Petitions, leaflets; general, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Political activisim; "The Defense Monitor;" newsletter of the Center for Defense Information, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Political activism; disarmament, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Political Activism; Vietnam, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Poor People's Campaign, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Poor People's Corporation, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Progressive Labor Party; welfare leaflets, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Project ENABLE, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Project Upward Bound, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Public Employees for Peace, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Public forum on social services; NYS DSS and NYC HRA, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Public Services Association, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Public works program; job assignments, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Puerto Rico, 1953; 1959; 1962 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Queens Council for Social Welfare, Inc.; special family counseling program, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Queensboro Lung Association, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Radical Alliance of Social Service Workers, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Radical Alliance of Social Service Workers; typescript of speech on welfare program, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Radical Alliance of Social Service Workers; critique of Carter welfare reform program, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Radical education project, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Budget cuts; Reagan, Ronald, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Recommendations from the 1971 White House Conference on Aging (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Report on the National Youth Administration, 1935-1937 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Republican Study Committee; "Presenting Welfare 'Reform'", 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Request for Fair Hearing sample letter, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Retirement, death and departure announcements; DSS, HRA (Box 12, Folder 10)
- St. Nicholas Social Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Salary Review Board, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- San Quentin Six, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Segal, Albert, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
- SANE (National Committee for Sane Nuclear Policy): Trade Union Division, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Serve the People: An Activists' Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Shorefront Jewish Community of Brooklyn (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): Community Action Committee (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): Elections, 1967-1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): Health (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): Members for a Militant Caucus, n.d.; 1967 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Timetable of Operations During Strike (Boro Hall), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Activists Lists (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Bulletin, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Case Aides, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Certification, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: Bureau of Public Assistance (BPA) (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: Casework, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: Clinton, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: HRA, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: Shelter & Institutional Employees, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: SSE (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Chapters: Supervisors, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Civil Liberties Activism (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Committee for a New Leadership, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Committee for a Solid Contract, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371:Community Relations and Services Committee, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Earmaking Committee, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Election Committee, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Executive Committee (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Finance Committee (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Legislative and Political Action Committee (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Rank and File Committee (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Reorganization and Workload Committee (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Service Committee (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Special Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Collective Bargaining Committee, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Constitutions (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Contracts (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Correspondence, General (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Delegates and Trustee Elections (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Delegates Assembly (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Educational Fund, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Elections (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Frank Barbaro Endorsement, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Leaflets, Circulars, 1969- (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: General (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Grievance Board, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Jurisdiction List, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Members for a Better Union, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Membership Counts (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Memos to Gorelick (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Clippings (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Notes (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: New York State ALF-CIO (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Organizational Newsletters (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Position Papers, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: "Purchase Power," Consumer Benefit Plans (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Pfefferman, Robert S.: "From Seperation to Title XX: The Worker's Story", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Training (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371:Union Funds Misappropriation Charges, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Welfare Fund (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Social Work Papers (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371: Work Stoppage, June-July, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Social Security and Welfare Legislation, 1950-1963 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Social Work Papers (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Social Workers for Civil Rights Action, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Social Workers for Lindsay, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Report by Mead, Richard H.: "Some Effects of Turnover on the Composition of the Welfare Caseland", 1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- State University of New York Medical Center, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Spanish Refugee Aid, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Strike, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Strikes: Social Workers, General, 1966-1967; 1972 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Students for a Democratic Society (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Stuyvesant Community Center, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Supervisor's Manual (Draft), n.d. (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Tambeau, William, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Task Force on City Owned Property (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Task Force on the New York City Crisis (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Task Force on Social Services, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Task Force on Welfare Issues, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Tenants (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Thornton, Pauline, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Trade Unionists for Peace (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Transport Workers Union: Contract Information, June 1978 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Typescript on State of Welfare System (56 pp., Author Unidentified), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- United for Workers, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 31)
- United Nations Support Group, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 32)